Hello friends welcome to my YouTube channel and
today in this video I will
tell you about insurance recording and what you are seeing in front of me is
a copy of ICC Lombard's insurance policy, there are many
things written in it, so
I will tell you everything one by one
and what are the addons and reliefs
in this policy, I will clear all those things for you
in this video, so let's
start the video and first of all
as you are seeing, this is written on the top,
this is your insurance policy number relief,
what is the position number of your vehicle, after that you are seeing below, Audi is
written, DP is written,
tenure is written, so what is the relief of all this,
10 air date is written in it, so we will go
down and explain it, right now the policy which you are
seeing is the
policy of Activa Aate smart vehicle insurance and
here I have highlighted the manufacturing thing, the
chassis number is already
given, you can check the engine number here,
after that what you are seeing are
all the addons  Which are the
add-ons, we will discuss all these in detail now,
like you are seeing Basic
Zero
Voice, Apna Basic Third Party Live
[Music]
Tax of Honda Driver, what are
all these terms,
I will tell you the full details of all these in the recording, so first of all we will
talk about our
Basic and Damage, what is this thing, Basic
on Damage Relief of your vehicle,
in simple language, 50% coverage is the basic
account, which covers 50% of the claim ratio of your vehicle, in case of any
other accident, so your basic damage
relief is valid till 15 years, you
can opt for it till 15 years, your claim ratio is based on your
insurance policy,
after this, what you are seeing is Zero Depression,
Zero Depression Mens, your claim ratio is 90 to
100% relief and you can opt for Zero type, which is 10
years, only up to five years of starting,
after that any
small insurance of this company which gives you Zero Depth  It will
not give you the option of basic on damage for your two wheeler or four
wheeler, in that
only you can take zero
type off,
so in the invoice you will get the
full ex-showroom theft certificate of your vehicle, which will be given to you,
after that if we talk about basic third
party, then this tax relief is ideal, if
someone's vehicle gets damaged due to your option, then
your basic third party provides the claim, the
insurance company
provides the claim ratio to the third party and now
your owner driver relief of Rs. 15 lakhs,
this is taxed only to the driver in
whose name the RC of the vehicle is, it
comes after that
and this tax is levied on any accident that happens to
you the day after tomorrow
[Music],
it is mentioned here
and I have highlighted all this that you
can take this claim, how can you take it and
when will you get this claim, you can take this claim
from their company and all their other insurance companies
if there is a death with them.  So this nominee can
go there and opt for it himself, you must have
mentioned the nominee in the insurance policy
and with them the disability is the owner
driver himself, for this he has to take the help
from the insurance company, if you found this
video of mine informative about recording
insurance then you can subscribe to my channel Motor Blog, do
like, share and comment,
if you like this video of mine,
I will keep making more informative
videos, if you have any doubt then you can
comment on this video of mine,
I will definitely reply to you